Have some more.
Black Maria?
Hey, why aren't you working on your task?
And what task would that be?
The search for my idiot son!
Oh, what's the harm, Viceroy Kaido?
They can handle the search
just fine without me.
I'd rather be here.
Okay, fine! It's that time of year again
to set aside rank and let loose!
Right, Orochi?!
It's an excellent day!
Right you are, Kaido!
The ghosts of the Kozuki Clan that
haunted us for twenty years are finally gone!
It's a day for celebration!
Kanjuro had them all fooled
until the very last minute,
and now his career is complete
after twenty long years!
He'll soon arrive with the captains
who sank the Red Scabbards into the sea!
He's an impressive one!
I could have easily killed him
back then without realizing it.
It's too bad though...
Even after earning all that trust,
Oden never opened up to him.
It's likely those samurai retainers
have not heard anything about it either.
Are you talking about...?
Yeah...
The key to the location of Laugh Tale,
the last island that Roger reached.
Who are you?!
Pardon me!
I have business with Lord Orochi!
Oh! There you are, Kanjuro!
I've never seen him before.
You here for a fight?!
Calm down, you idiots!
He's Orochi's man!
It has been too long, Lord Orochi!
The mansion is so massive that
I got a little lost backstage.
I had to cut down all those men
who mistakenly attacked me as their enemy.
I apologize for that.
Well, that's alright!
Oh! I see you've got something there...
It is Kozuki Momonosuke, per your request.
He is Oden's son.
He cut his ropes and attempted to escape
on the way here, so I had to knock him out.
Do not fret. He is alive.
So this is how you treat
your former Kozuki lord's heir...
How cold and heartless of you!
Now that my act is over,
he's just another whelp to me.
What a surprise!
I do remember you.
You're one of the Nine Red Scabbards
that I fought against twenty years ago.
And you... I definitely remember you.
Your father was brave, but you're
nothing but a disappointment.
You haven't changed one bit in twenty years!
Indeed. He's nothing more
than a miserable brat...
who happened to inherit a great name.
You poor thing.
He's bleeding... How could you
strike a little boy so hard?
It's time to drink! Let's make a toast!
You've done well playing
the part of spy for so long!
Bravo!
No, Shogun Orochi!
I failed to intercept the Red Scabbards' plan...
because the Straw Hats
and their allies ambushed us!
What?! Failed?!
The rebel forces, 5,400 strong, are
advancing toward Onigashima as we speak!
Unacceptable!
You failed to intercept their plan?!
I am deeply sorry!
You're the one who told me that
they'd rendezvous at Tokage Port!
Why didn't you exterminate them?!
K-Kin'emon outsmarted me!
I have known him for a long time,
but I underestimated his tactical genius!
Stop with the excuses!
Answer me, Kanjuro!
Will the samurai fleet make it to Onigashima?!
It seems like we're still safe here, Shogun Orochi.
Fukurokuju!
There are no suspicious ships at the port.
However, three of our
warships have yet to return.
In fact, we have confirmation of four pirates
out on the Performance Floor.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
Soldier of Slaughter Killer.
It's very likely that the rest of their
crews are also on the island.
If you knew that, why didn't
you report it before?!
Sir Queen was handling it,
so I thought it'd be better
not to spoil the banquet.
Whether they're here or not, the fact remains
that all of our forces are here on Onigashima.
Whatever happens, this is
the safest place in the country!
You said it!
Drink up, Orochi!
Here, let me pour you a cup.
No... I don't want reassurances!
I want a report that
the damn samurai have been slain!
Luffy made it inside...
Keep yourself alive!
I'll rescue you for sure!
I must escape!
Black Maria!
Give him to me!
That's right! We mustn't forget!
He's the leader of the enemy force!
Set the execution stage!
Once the renowned Kozuki family dies out,
any sparks of loyalty left will fade away completely.
And it'll finally be over!
Luffy...!
Everyone...!
Father...!
Is that you, Cat?! You're late!
You only just arrived?!
Yeah!
We just climbed up the falls!
Don't you know what day and time it is?!
It's the night of the Fire Festival, so we're
just in time for the great battle, aren't we?
You-gara shouldn't say that until you get here.
We're already on our way to
the northwestern end of Onigashima.
Got it! See you later then!
No, wait!
Wait, hey!
Cat!
That impatience of his remains unchanged.
I just hope they make it in time for our raid.
I have not seen Kitty since we got separated...
I bet he's as big as Doggy now, too.
That damn cat... He'd better
get here as fast as he can!
We'll reach the rear door soon!
Because of the whirlpools, normal ships
can only approach the island from the front.
I hope Kin'emon and Denjiro
were able to reach the rear door safely.
Yes! I want all of us to fulfill
Lord Oden's wish together!
Lord Momonosuke...
Please be safe!
Are they all okay?
Yeah, of course they are!
He said everyone made it to the island
already, so I guess the raid is underway!
That lonely island is now
called Onigashima, huh?
Who would've thought that we'd arrive at the
same time, even though you left before me?
Turns out I didn't need to entrust you
with my message to Straw Hat Luffy!
You're right!
I'll throw this note out!
Anyway, I can't believe you came, Marco.
Well, I always did like Oden.
But I can't believe how much
his country has changed...
News about this place never crosses the sea.
I didn't know the once prosperous Wano
had been reduced to such a state...
It's all because of Kaido.
If you've made up your mind,
let's hurry on to Onigashima!
We must catch up to everyone!
But what can we do?
The raid has already begun.
How will we slip past
the enemy lines to join them?
Leave it to me!
I have an idea!
As planned, Denjiro is leading
the southern forces to the castle's rear door.
There seems to be a gate here!
Hide!
Is he a top officer?
What rotten luck!
Listen! Find him as quickly as possible!
– Yes, sir!
On the contrary, it seems we have lucked out.
I know him.
I will talk to him.
Who goes there?!
Wait, it's me!
Aren't you...?
It's been a while...
Sasaki!
Kyoshiro!
I heard you weren't coming this year!
Yeah, I ask that you keep this a secret.
You're here incognito? What happened to
that pompadour you were so proud of?
It's unusual to see you
away from the banquet.
Yeah. Kaido's kid went missing.
But hey, want a drink?
You bet I do!
Guys! Head back to the Skull Dome!
I'll join you later.
A gate that was missing from the blueprints.
And one of the Soaring Six, Sasaki.
Such obstacles would have been
difficult for Kyoshiro to overcome
if he wasn't so trusted by the enemy.
Seastone?!
Hey, what's the big idea, Kyoshiro?!
Restrain him!
– Yes, sir!
What's going on?! Hey!
Gag him as well!
– Yes, sir!
Answer me, Kyoshiro!
Hey, Sasaki...
How much do you know of Wano's history?
Is that...?!
After restraining one of
the formidable Soaring Six,
Denjiro split his group into two,
just as the eastern forces had.
Get to the dome from here!
Good luck!
Thus, the southern forces
are steadily closing in on Kaido!
Fire!
I won't let you get away!
I knew it wouldn't work!
Of course it didn't!
They're gone!
Chobro!
That's one fierce mature woman...
Even though they were frightened,
they still led her in the opposite direction...
We are in your debt,
Commander Chopper, Driver Usopp...
Let us carry on!
– Yeah!
Everyone! Do not let their sacrifice go to waste!
Hey, shouldn't we do something?!
I think that monstrous mature woman
is too much for those two boys to handle!
She's right!
It's Big Mom!
I know!
That's why there's nothing we can do!
Let's just be happy they lured her away!
In any case, why's it so hot in here?
Nami! Look up!
We're in trouble!
I found you!
It's the woman who kidnapped Zeus, Mama!
Fight, Pay-Pay! Fight, Pay-Pay!
Hey! Go look somewhere else, you bonehead!
Excuse me, Pay-Pay?!
How dare you...!
But...
I can't run anymore...
Pay-Pay! I'm ever so weary!
Woe is me!
Don't cry about it to me!
If you're tired, just sit there!
You're supposed to offer...
Oh, no!
...to carry me on your back!
Hey, get off of me! Hey!
Wait! Let go of me! Big Sis!
You little...
Hey! Stop it! I mean it!
Pay-Pay?!
Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay!
Stay with me, stay with me, stay with me!
Oh no, my Pay-Pay!
What's that?
Pay-Pay!
Pay-Pay sacrificed himself to save me!
Who the hell are you?!
There it is... Onigashima.
King...
Marco...
Straw Hat...
They'd better prepare
themselves for a licking...
And no, I don't approve of Mama's alliance!
The Big Mom Pirates will have the last lick!
What now, Usopp?!
Big Mom turned back
to go after Nami and the others!
I guess she's trying to take back Zeus.
I'm worried about them...
The transformation switch seems
to have activated when she punched us.
Well, I'm sure they'll be fine...
Sanji's with them, too.
Sanji, huh?
I hope he remembers to rescue Momonosuke
instead of chasing women in the pleasure hall.
I wouldn't rule that out...
But let's trust Sanji!
Yeah!
Kin'emon's team was able
to advance, so we're doing well!
We showed them what
the Brachio-Tank is capable of!
Yeah! We're Commander Chopper and
gunner Usopp driving the Brachio-Tank 5!
Nothing stands in our way!
Come along...
An old umbrella.
Old clogs and old sandals.
A dirt wall!
A candle!
A lantern, too!
I give you life!
So follow me.
Mama, this way!
Hey! Stop calling for Big Mom, sun!
What should I do, Nami?!
If she catches me, I'm a goner!
Is that overripe mature woman
really that dangerous?
She's on a whole different level!
Hey, didn't we see Sanji a little while ago?
Yeah!
Oh, but...
Sorry for making you worry...
I'm not giving up on finding those women!
What did he even come here for?!
In any case, we need to outrun her
and look for Lord Momonosuke!
Okay!
Mama! This way!
There's no need to rush.
The Performance Floor is just ahead.
There's nowhere to run.
So many of these guys have powers…
Call us Gifters.
We, too, once aimed to be King of the Pirates.
If you bow down to Lord Kaido,
things will be easier for you.
There are almost 500 of us.
Don't make this hard on yourself.
It's not too late to start over.
Kid! I told you it's too reckless
to break through head-on!
We got separated from Heat and the others...
They were fighting right alongside us,
but they'll be okay on their own.
If we kill you guys, I bet we'll get promoted!
Please stop!
Lord Kaido is looking for you!
Stop bothering me!
Leave me alone!
– Young Master! Please stop!
Let down your guard and you die!
Pay-Pay!
Pay-Pay! Are you okay?!
Don't leave me! I'd be ever so distraught!
Hey, you!
How could you...
How could you do this to Pay-Pay?!
Don't you dare bully my Pay-Pay!
You're the one who used him
to ski down the stairs.
What's your name?!
Who do you work for
and which unit do you belong to?!
No, Big Sis...
He's an intruder.
What?!
I'm Luffy.
The man who'll become the King of the Pirates!
Do you have any idea
whose castle you're standing in?
The one who will become
King of the Pirates is obviously Lord Kaido!
You freaking dumbass!
I'll cave your damn skull in!
A headbutt?!
Ulti-Mortar!
Hey, Big Sis!
I know...
Pay-Pay too?
Yeah!
Excuse me, but...
why did you two transform?!
Master Ulti!
Master Page One!
Master Ulti?
Um...
Quiet down, you.
We did it because...
this guy is the real deal!
No, no, there's no way!
You hit his skull so hard, he's gotta be dead!
Then how do you explain that haki?!
That hurt!
These guys are amazing...
and there are so many of them.
I was wrong...
to underestimate you.
This castle belongs to an Emperor!
Listen up, ya jerks!
Shogun Orochi presents
an impromptu special event starting now!
Everyone!
Let me introduce this brat...
Lo and behold...
the son of Kozuki Oden,
thought to have died twenty years ago!
Gum-Gum...
Big Sis!
Elephant Gun!
– Master Page One!
– Are you okay?!
Master Page One...
You damn rat bastard...!
How dare you do that to Pay-Pay?!
I'll destroy you!
Master Ulti turned into a dinosaur, too!
Please! The castle can't take much more!
She's... so strong!
Ulti-Meteor!
Oh no!
Gear Fourth!
Thunder Bagua!
Straw Hat Luffy!
It's you, isn't it?!
That's me.
I...
Who are you?!
He's getting away!
Catch him!
I'm sorry!
I'm not gonna hurt you!
Yeah, you don't seem like you will...
Listen, I gotta go!
I've been waiting for you!
Finally! You're finally here!
Indeed, I've been waiting for you!
Waiting for so very long!
My name is Yamato!
I'm Kaido's son!